<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Kurin_OnSkin_Shirt.description>A large, baggy shirt with a collar and buttons. It's great to wear at any time unless it's very hot.</Kurin_OnSkin_Shirt.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_T_Shirt.description>A nice T-shirt to wear in hot summer.</Kurin_OnSkin_T_Shirt.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Hot_Pants.description>Light summer pants. Sunscreen is essential to avoid burning skin on sunny days.</Kurin_OnSkin_Hot_Pants.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Pajamas.description>Very comfortable pajamas. Great for a good night's sleep, even for those who suffer from insomnia.</Kurin_OnSkin_Pajamas.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_One_Piece_Dress.description>A moderately light dress. It looks very innocent!</Kurin_OnSkin_One_Piece_Dress.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Open_Back_Knit.description>The cut is largely dug on one side. There is still some debate among Kurins how to wear it.</Kurin_OnSkin_Open_Back_Knit.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Open_Shoulder_Knit.description>A cute open shoulder knit. It's very comfortable and soft, great for long naps.</Kurin_OnSkin_Open_Shoulder_Knit.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Hoodie.description>This is a large size hoodie that is great for active wear.</Kurin_OnSkin_Hoodie.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Casual_Wear.description>A popular casual wear for Kurin. Blends both comfort and style.</Kurin_OnSkin_Casual_Wear.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Gothic_Dress.description>Gothic dress. Always old-fashioned: anytime, anywhere.</Kurin_OnSkin_Gothic_Dress.description>
    
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Military_Uniform.description>Combat military uniform with plasteel bulletproof plates. Light and warm, it ensures a good amount of defense. Its ergonomic design also significantly increases the wearer's ranged combat power.</Kurin_OnSkin_Military_Uniform.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Nun_Dress.description>An exceptional nun dress that stands out.</Kurin_OnSkin_Nun_Dress.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Work_Jumpsuit.description>It is the uniform of a technician working in the red fox armory. Not only are there pockets for storing various tools and parts, but they are also made of a material that is not damaged or contaminated by oil or sparks.</Kurin_OnSkin_Work_Jumpsuit.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Traditional_Simple_Dress.description>Pure white dress with a pink skirt, impressive Kurin apparel.</Kurin_OnSkin_Traditional_Simple_Dress.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Traditional_Fancy_Dress.description>A gorgeous blue and white body-length dress, adorned with a shawl. Socially impressive Kurin apparel.</Kurin_OnSkin_Traditional_Fancy_Dress.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Traditional_Luxury_Dress.description>This Kurin traditional apparel features a brown see-through skirt and shirt.</Kurin_OnSkin_Traditional_Luxury_Dress.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Cute_Dress.description>It is a very cute dress. Kurins often wear it for festivals.</Kurin_OnSkin_Cute_Dress.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Seductive_White_Dress.description>A very seductive white dress with one skirt open.</Kurin_OnSkin_Seductive_White_Dress.description>
  
  <Kurin_OnSkin_Seductive_Black_Dress.description>A very seductive black dress with one skirt open.</Kurin_OnSkin_Seductive_Black_Dress.description>
  
</LanguageData>